#### Contact

7842790600 (Mobile) ibadullabaig@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ibadulla-baig-2479a0145 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Internet of Things (IoT)
Design Thinking

**Professional Ethics** 

### Languages

Hindi (Native or Bilingual) English (Professional Working) Telugu

#### Certifications

Design Thinking
Product development

#### Honors-Awards

Token of honor Token of honor

# Ibadulla Baig

Intern - T-Tribe program at T-Hub Foundation Hyderabad

## Summary

Experienced Internet of Things Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the education management industry. Skilled in design thinking, Engineering, Entrepreneurship. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Technology focused on Instrumentation from VNR Vignanajyothi Institute of Engineering & Technology.

# Experience

T-Hub Hyderabad Intern June 2020 - Present (3 months) IIIT HYD, Gachibowli

Idealabs FutureTech Ventures
IoT Engineer
January 2019 - June 2020 (1 year 6 months)
Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Ganapathi sugar industries private limited Ganapathi sugar industries private limited May 2015 - November 2015 (7 months) Sangareddi, Telangana, India

## Education

VNR Vignanajyothi Institute of Engineering & Technology Bachelor of Technology, Instrumentation · (2016 - 2019)

A.A.N.M & V.V.R.S.R polytechnic

Diploma, Applied Electornics and instrumentation · (2013 - 2016)